<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Muvlex</string>

    <!--UI texts-->
    <string name="active_language">English</string>
    <string name="select_language">Select language</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="log_in">Log in</string>
    <string name="email_or_username">Email or username</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign up</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot password?</string>
    <string name="get_help">Get help</string>
    <string name="email_address">Email address</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_muvlex">Welcome to Muvlex</string>
    <string name="pick_a_username_for_your_account_you_can_always_change_it_later">
        Pick a username for your account. You can always change it later.
    </string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="by_clicking_next_you_agree_to_our_privacy_policy_terms_conditions">
        By clicking Next, you agree to our <b>Privacy Policy</b>, <b>Terms &amp; Conditions</b>.
    </string>
    <string name="username_not_available">Username not available</string>
    <string name="username_can_only_use_letters_numbers_underscores_and_periods">
        Username can only use letters, numbers, underscores, and periods
    </string>
    <string name="username_cannot_be_empty">Username cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="success">Success</string>
    <string name="find_your_account">Find Your Account</string>
    <string name="enter_your_username_or_the_email_linked_to_your_account">
        Enter your username or the email linked to your account.
    </string>
    <string name="okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="resend">Resend</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="movies">Movies</string>
    <string name="series">Series</string>
    <string name="users">Users</string>
    <string name="searching_for">Searching for</string>
    <string name="no_results_found_for">No Results Found for</string>
    <string name="unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="rate_this_movie">Rate this movie</string>
    <string name="share_your_thoughts_with_other">Share your thoughts with others</string>
    <string name="write_a_review">Write a review</string>
    <string name="overview">Overview</string>
    <string name="post">Post</string>
    <string name="reviews_are_public_and_editable">Reviews are public and editable</string>
    <string name="the_name_and_photo_on_your_muvlex_profile_will_appear_with_your_review_please_do_a_fair_rate_and_write_a_relevant_review_about_the_movie_or_series_so_the_other_users_can_get_benefit_from_it">The name and photo on your Muvlex profile will appear with your review. Please, do a fair rate and write a relevant review about the movie or series so the other users can get benefit from it.</string>
    <string name="got_it">Got it</string>
    <string name="learn_more">Learn more</string>
    <string name="describe_your_experience_optional">Describe your experience (optional)</string>
    <string name="discard_draft">Discard draft?</string>
    <string name="keep">Keep</string>
    <string name="discard">Discard</string>
    <string name="rate_this_series">Rate this series</string>
    <string name="blank_message" translatable="false"> </string>
    <string name="follow">Follow</string>
    <string name="unfollow">Unfollow</string>
    <string name="posts">Posts</string>
    <string name="followers">Followers</string>
    <string name="following">Following</string>
    <string name="search_result_will_appear_here">Search result will appear here</string>
    <string name="users_posts_will_appear_here">User\'s posts will appear here</string>
    <string name="edit_profile">Edit Profile</string>
    <string name="your_posts_will_appear_here">Your posts will appear here</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign out</string>
    <string name="posts_will_appear_here">Posts will appear here</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="bio">Bio</string>

    <!--Alert texts-->
    <string name="creating_user">Creating user</string>
    <string name="your_account_is_successfully_created_verify_your_account_by_checking_your_email_address">
        Your account is successfully created, verify your account by checking your email address.
    </string>
    <string name="saving">Saving</string>
    <string name="sending_verification_code">Sending verification</string>
    <string name="checking_username">Checking username</string>
    <string name="logging_in">Logging in</string>
    <string name="loading_user_data">Loading data</string>
    <string name="sending_password_reset_email">Sending password reset</string>
    <string name="follow_the_link_we_have_sent_to_your_email_address_to_reset_your_muvlex_password">
        Follow the link we have sent to your email address to reset your Muvlex password.
    </string>
    <string name="sorry_we_were_unable_to_log_in_to_your_account_due_to_email_verification_verify_your_email_to_continue">
        Sorry, we were unable to log in to your account due to email verification. Verify your email to continue.
    </string>

    <!--Image descriptions-->
    <string name="logo">Logo</string>
    <string name="change_language">Change language</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="poster">Poster</string>
    <string name="star">Star</string>
    <string name="calendar">Calendar</string>
    <string name="vote_average">Vote average</string>
    <string name="genre">Genre</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="profile_picture">Profile picture</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>

    <!--Toast texts-->
    <string name="something_went_wrong_try_again_later">Something went wrong, try again later</string>
    <string name="passwords_dont_match">Passwords don\'t match</string>
    <string name="enter_a_valid_email_address">Enter a valid email address</string>
    <string name="password_should_be_at_least_6_characters">Password should be at least 6 characters</string>
    <string name="email_address_is_already_in_use_by_another_account">Email address is already in use by another account</string>
    <string name="no_internet_connection">No internet connection</string>
    <string name="verify_your_email_address_to_continue">Verify your email address to continue</string>
    <string name="we_couldnt_find_info_for_this_account">We couldn\'t find info for this account</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Invalid password</string>
    <string name="check_your_email_to_verify_your_muvlex_account">Check your email to verify your Muvlex account</string>
    <string name="email_address_is_already_verified">Email address is already verified</string>
    <string name="there_are_no_email_clients_installed">There are no email clients installed</string>
    <string name="you_have_just_shared_a_new_review">You\'ve just shared a new review</string>

    <!--Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions-->
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_content">
        Murad Ismayilov built the Muvlex app as an ad-supported app.
         This service is provided by Murad Ismayilov at no cost and is intended for use as is.
        \n\nThis page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information if anyone decided to use my service.
        \n\nIf you choose to use my service, then you agree to the collection and use of information about this policy.
         The personal information that I collect is used for providing and improving the service.
         I will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this privacy policy.
        \n\nThe terms used in this privacy policy have the same meanings as in our terms and conditions, which are accessible at Muvlex unless otherwise defined in this privacy policy.
    </string>
    <string name="information_collection_and_use">Information Collection and Use</string>
    <string name="information_collection_and_use_content">
        For a better experience, while using our service, I may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to an email address, username, profile picture, user biography, the followers of a user, the users which a user follows, posts of a user, saved posts of a user, the posts which a user has liked, the posts which a user has commented, the comments of a user.
        \n\nThe app does use third-party services that may collect information used to identify you.
        \n\nLink to the privacy policy of third-party service providers used by the app
    </string>
    <string name="google_play_services">Google Play Services</string>
    <string name="google_analytics_for_firebase">Google Analytics for Firebase</string>
    <string name="firebase_crashlytics">Firebase Crashlytics</string>
    <string name="facebook">Facebook</string>
    <string name="log_data">Log Data</string>
    <string name="log_data_content">
        I want to inform you that whenever you use my service, in case of an error in the app I collect data and information (through third-party products) on your phone called log data.
         This log data may include information such as your device internet protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing my service, the time and date of your use of the service, and other statistics.
    </string>
    <string name="cookies">Cookies</string>
    <string name="cookies_content">
        Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers.
         These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your device\'s internal memory.
        \n\nThis service does not use these “cookies” explicitly.
         However, the app may use third-party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collect information and improve their services.
    </string>
    <string name="service_providers">Service Providers</string>
    <string name="service_providers_content">
        I may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:
        \n\n* To facilitate our service;
        \n* To provide the service on our behalf;
        \n* To perform service-related services; or
        \n* To assist us in analyzing how our service is used.
        \n\nI want to inform users of this service that these third-parties have access to their personal information.
         The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf.
         However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.
    </string>
    <string name="security">Security</string>
    <string name="security_content">
        I value your trust in providing us your personal information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it.
         But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and I cannot guarantee its absolute security.
    </string>
    <string name="links_to_other_sites">Links to Other Sites</string>
    <string name="links_to_other_sites_content">
        This service may contain links to other sites.
         If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site.
         Note that these external sites are not operated by me.
         Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the privacy policy of these websites.
         I have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.
    </string>
    <string name="children_s_privacy">Children’s Privacy</string>
    <string name="children_s_privacy_content">
        These services do not address anyone under the age of 13.
         I do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13.
         In the case I discover that a child under 13 has provided me with personal information, I immediately delete this from our servers.
         If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact me so that I will be able to do the necessary actions.
    </string>
    <string name="changes_to_this_privacy_policy">Changes to This Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="changes_to_this_privacy_policy_content">
        I may update our privacy policy from time to time.
         Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes.
         I will notify you of any changes by posting the new privacy policy on this page.
    </string>
    <string name="this_policy_is_effective_as_of">This policy is effective as of</string>
    <string name="effective_date">2021–02–23</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="contact_us_content">
        If you have any questions or suggestions about my privacy policy, do not hesitate to contact me at
    </string>
    <string name="muvlexapp_gmail_com">muvlexapp@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="this_privacy_policy_page_was_created_at">This privacy policy page was created at</string>
    <string name="privacypolicytemplate_net">privacypolicytemplate.net</string>
    <string name="and_modified_generated_by">and modified/generated by</string>
    <string name="app_privacy_policy_generator">App Privacy Policy Generator</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">Terms &amp; Conditions</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_content_0">
        By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore that you read them carefully before using the app.
         You’re not allowed to copy or modify the app, any part of the app, or our trademarks in any way.
         You’re not allowed to attempt to extract the source code of the app, and you also shouldn’t try to translate the app into other languages or make derivative versions.
         The app itself, and all the trademarks, copyright, database rights, and other intellectual property rights related to it, still belong to Murad Ismayilov.
        \n\nMurad Ismayilov is committed to ensuring that the app is as useful and efficient as possible.
         For that reason, we reserve the right to make changes to the app or to charge for its services, at any time and for any reason.
         We will never charge you for the app or its services without making it very clear to you exactly what you’re paying for.
        \n\nThe Muvlex app stores and processes the personal data that you have provided to us, to provide my service.
         It’s your responsibility to keep your phone and access to the app secure.
         We, therefore, recommend that you do not jailbreak or root your phone, which is the process of removing software restrictions and limitations imposed by the official operating system of your device.
         It could make your phone vulnerable to malware/viruses/malicious programs, compromise your phone’s security features and it could mean that the Muvlex app won’t work properly or at all.
        \n\nThe app does use third-party services that declare its terms and conditions.
        \n\nLink to terms and conditions of third-party service providers used by the app
    </string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_content_1">
        You should be aware that there are certain things that Murad Ismayilov will not take responsibility for.
         Certain functions of the app will require the app to have an active internet connection.
         The connection can be Wi-Fi or provided by your mobile network provider, but Murad Ismayilov cannot take responsibility for the app not working at full functionality if you don’t have access to Wi-Fi, and you don’t have any of your data allowance left.
        \n\nIf you’re using the app outside of an area with Wi-Fi, you should remember that your terms of the agreement with your mobile network provider will still apply.
         As a result, you may be charged by your mobile provider for the cost of data for the duration of the connection while accessing the app, or other third-party charges.
         In using the app, you’re accepting responsibility for any such charges, including roaming data charges if you use the app outside of your home territory (i.e. region or country) without turning off data roaming.
         If you are not the bill payer for the device on which you’re using the app, please be aware that we assume that you have received permission from the bill payer for using the app.
        \n\nAlong the same lines, Murad Ismayilov cannot always take responsibility for the way you use the app i.e.
         You need to make sure that your device stays charged – if it runs out of battery and you can’t turn it on to avail of the service, Murad Ismayilov cannot accept responsibility.
        \n\nConcerning Murad Ismayilov’s responsibility for your use of the app, when you’re using the app, it’s important to bear in mind that although we endeavor to ensure that it is updated and correct at all times, we do rely on third parties to provide information to us so that we can make it available to you.
         Murad Ismayilov accepts no liability for any loss, direct or indirect, you experience as a result of relying wholly on this functionality of the app.
        \n\nAt some point, we may wish to update the app.
         The app is currently available on Android – the requirements for the system(and for any additional systems we decide to extend the availability of the app to) may change, and you’ll need to download the updates if you want to keep using the app.
         Murad Ismayilov does not promise that it will always update the app so that it is relevant to you and/or works with the Android version that you have installed on your device.
         However, you promise to always accept updates to the application when offered to you, We may also wish to stop providing the app, and may terminate use of it at any time without giving notice of termination to you.
         Unless we tell you otherwise, upon any termination, (a) the rights and licenses granted to you in these terms will end; (b) you must stop using the app, and (if needed) delete it from your device.
    </string>
    <string name="changes_to_this_terms_and_conditions">Changes to This Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="changes_to_this_terms_and_conditions_content">I may update our terms and conditions from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new terms and conditions on this page.</string>
    <string name="this_terms_and_conditions_page_was_generated_by">This terms and conditions page was generated by</string>

    <!--Ratings & review policy-->
    <string name="ratings_and_review_on_the_muvlex">Ratings &amp; review on the Muvlex</string>
    <string name="ratings_and_review_on_the_muvlex_content">
        On this page, you can find information about Muvlex\'s policies for posting reviews.
        \nYou can write reviews for anything that you\'ve watched.
         Reviews are a great way to help others decide what to watch by telling them about your experience.
         Muvlex doesn\'t pay anyone to rate or review content on Muvlex, and we expect reviewers to be honest and unbiased.
    </string>
    <string name="ratings_and_reviews_posting_policies">Ratings and reviews posting policies</string>
    <string name="ratings_and_reviews_posting_policies_content">
        Ratings and reviews are meant to be helpful and trustworthy.
         Reviewing content on Muvlex is a great way to share helpful feedback and assist other Muvlex users in finding great content, movies &amp; series.
        \nGuidelines for writing a good review
        \n* Make your reviews useful and informative.
        \n* Try to include both positives and drawbacks.
        \n* Keep it readable; check grammar and spelling, and don\'t use excessive capitalization and punctuation.
        \n* Be nice to others.
        \nMuvlex\'s policies for ratings and reviews are below.
         Reviews that don\'t follow these policies will be removed, and anyone who repeatedly or egregiously violates them may lose the ability to post reviews on Muvlex.
    </string>
    <string name="spam_and_fake_reviews">Spam and fake reviews</string>
    <string name="spam_and_fake_reviews_content">
        Your reviews should reflect the experiences that you\'ve had with the content, movie &amp; series that you\'re reviewing.
        \n* Don\'t post fake or inaccurate reviews.
        \n* Don\'t post the same review multiple times.
        \n* Don\'t post reviews for the same content from multiple accounts.
        \n* Don\'t post reviews to mislead other users or manipulate the rating.
        \n* Don\'t post reviews on behalf of others.
        \n* Don\'t misrepresent your identity or your connection to the content that you\'re reviewing.
    </string>
    <string name="off_topic_reviews">Off-topic reviews</string>
    <string name="off_topic_reviews_content">
        Keep reviews on-topic and relevant to the content, service, or experience that you\'re reviewing.
        \n* Don\'t post solicitations, political, or social commentary or anything else that is irrelevant to the content, service, or experience that you\'re reviewing.
    </string>
    <string name="advertising">Advertising</string>
    <string name="advertising_content">
        We want reviews to be useful, and they aren\'t useful if they\'re promoting something other than the content or service that you\'re reviewing.
        \n* Don\'t post promotional or commercial content for any products or services, including affiliate or referral-based promotions.
        \n* Don\'t post phone numbers, email addresses, or links to other websites.
    </string>
    <string name="conflict_of_interest">Conflict of interest</string>
    <string name="conflict_of_interest_content">
        Reviews are most valuable when they\'re genuine and unbiased.
         They should be written by people who aren\'t motivated by financial gain.
        \n* Don\'t offer or accept money, products, or services in exchange for posting reviews.
        \n* Don\'t review content, movies &amp; series or experiences if you own or work for the business that created it.
    </string>
    <string name="copyrighted_content">Copyrighted content</string>
    <string name="copyrighted_content_content">
        Reviews should be your own and reflect your personal opinions.
        \n* Don\'t post reviews that infringe on the intellectual property rights of others, including copyright.
    </string>
    <string name="personal_and_confidential_information">Personal and confidential information</string>
    <string name="personal_and_confidential_information_content">
        Reviews are meant to share experiences, and you can express the way that you feel about something without revealing sensitive personal information.
        \n* Don\'t post personal or confidential information, such as a physical address or driver\'s license number.
    </string>
    <string name="illegal_content">Illegal content</string>
    <string name="illegal_content_content">
        Your reviews must comply with the law and any terms or legal agreements that you have agreed to.
        \n* Don\'t post reviews that contain or link to illegal content.
    </string>
    <string name="sexually_explicit_content">Sexually explicit content</string>
    <string name="sexually_explicit_content_content">
        Muvlex is intended for a broad audience, and reviews should reflect that.
        \n* Don\'t post reviews that contain, promote, or solicit sexually explicit content.
        \n* Don\'t  post reviews that depict children in sexual situations or address them in a sexual manner.
    </string>
    <string name="hate_speech">Hate speech</string>
    <string name="hate_speech_content">
        Muvlex is intended for all people, and reviews should reflect that.
        \n* Don\'t promote violence, condone violence or incite hatred against an individual or group based on their race, nationality, ethnic origin, religion, gender, gender identity, sexual orientation, age, disability, veteran status, or any other characteristic that is associated with systemic discrimination or marginalization.
    </string>
    <string name="offensive_reviews">Offensive reviews</string>
    <string name="offensive_reviews_content">
        Muvlex is meant to entertain and inform, not attack and offend.
        \n* Don\'t post obscene, profane, or offensive language.
        \n* Don\'t post reviews that harass, bully or attack others.
    </string>

    <string-array name="primaryLanguage">
        <item>English</item>
        <item>Türkçe</item>
        <item>Azəricə</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="secondaryLanguage">
        <item>-</item>
        <item>Turkish</item>
        <item>Azerbaijani</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
